{
    "title": "The Quiz",
    "marking": "none",
    "rounds": [{
        "name": "Setup",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Enter your name:",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Any"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "General Knowledge Round üåç",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Name the protagonist in the Back to the Future series of movies.",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Marty McFly"
        }, {
            "question": "What three mountains comprise the Three Peaks challenge?",
            "type": "multiple-answer",
            "answers": ["Ben Nevis", "Scarfell Pike", "Snowdonia"]
        }, {
            "question": "What cocktail is made with Tomato Juice, Tabasco and Vodka?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Bloody Mary"
        }, {
            "question": "The Tour De France ends in which city?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Paris"
        }, {
            "question": "In which city can the Liberty Bell be found?",
            "type": "multiple-choice",
            "answer": "Philadelphia",
            "choices": [
                "New York",
                "Boston",
                "Philadelphia",
                "Washington, D.C."
            ]
        }, {
            "question": "Name three land-locked European countries?",
            "type": "multiple-answer",
            "scoring": [{
                "answers": 3,
                "awards": 1,
                "awarded-for": "all-correct"
            }],
            "answers": [
                "Andorra",
                "Austria",
                "Belarus",
                "Czech Republic",
                "Hungary",
                "Liechtenstein",
                "Luxembourg",
                "Macedonia",
                "Moldova",
                "San Marino",
                "Serbia",
                "Slovakia",
                "Switzerland",
                "Vatican City"
            ]
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "London Round üá¨üáß",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Which tube line terminates at West Ruislip?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Central"
        }, {
            "question": "Which country donates the Trafalgar Square Christmas tree each year as a thanks for British efforts in WWII?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Norway"
        }, {
            "question": "What‚Äôs the airport code for London Heathrow?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "LHR"
        }, {
            "question": "What‚Äôs the real name of the Walkie Talkie building?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "20 Fenchurch Street"
        }, {
            "question": "How many ravens are there in the Tower of London?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "7"
        }, {
            "question": "Name the tower that houses Big Ben?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Elizabeth Tower"
        }, {
            "question": "In which borough would you find Pentonville prison?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Islington"
        }, {
            "question": "Which famous talkshow host was born in the London Underground?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Jerry Springer"
        }, {
            "question": "Which sport is played at Lord‚Äôs?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Cricket"
        }, {
            "question": "Which London Underground station is named after a football team?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Arsenal"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Technology Round ü§ñ",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "Name the other two founders of Apple along with Steve Jobs?",
            "type": "multiple-answer",
            "answers": [
                "Steve Wosniak",
                "Ronald Wayne"
            ]
        }, {
            "question": "What does ADSL stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Asymmetric Digital Subscriber Line"
        }, {
            "question": "Which website, particularly popular in the Noughties, was born from an idea invented by Steve and Julie Pankhurst from Barnet, North London?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Friends Reunited"
        }, {
            "question": "To which country does the top-level domain .mc belong?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Monaco"
        }, {
            "question": "Which science-fiction writer devised the Three Laws of Robotics?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Isaac Asimov"
        }, {
            "question": "In which U.S. state are the headquarters of Microsoft?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Washington"
        }, {
            "question": "Written in 1990, ‚ÄòArchie‚Äô was the first ever what?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Internet Search Engine"
        }, {
            "question": "An SD card is a memory card format frequently used in portable devices such as mobile phones and cameras ‚Äì what does SD stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Secure Digital"
        }, {
            "question": "A bit is the smallest possible unit of data in a computer, what does it stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Binary Digit"
        }, {
            "question": "What are the first names of Nintendo‚Äôs Super Mario Brothers?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Mario and Luigi"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Text Round üì±",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "What is the abbreviation TYVM short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Thank you very much"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation B4N short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Bye for now"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation ROTFLMAO short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Rolling on the floor laughing my ass off"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation TTYL short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Talk to you later"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation LOL short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Laugh out loud"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation IMHO short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "In my humble opinion"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation HAND short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Have a nice day"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation YOLO short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "You only live once"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation PPL short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "People"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the abbreviation IRL short for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "In real life"
        }]
    }, {
        "name": "Terminal Round üñ•",
        "questions": [{
            "question": "What does the command CD stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Change directory"
        }, {
            "question": "What command would you use if you wanted more information about another Terminal command?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Man"
        }, {
            "question": "What command can you use to display the last 10 lines of input?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Tail"
        }, {
            "question": "What does BASH stand for?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Bourne Again Shell"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the name of the default shell that comes with macOS Catalina?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "ZSH"
        }, {
            "question": "The Terminal is the name of a 2004 comedy starring which actor?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Tom Hanks"
        }, {
            "question": "What is name of the constant speed that a freely falling object eventually reaches when the resistance of the medium through which it is falling prevents further acceleration?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Terminal Velocity"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the terminal station on the Victoria line northbound?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Walthamstow"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the name of the shell provided with the Windows operating system?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "DOS"
        }, {
            "question": "What is the name of the original Unix shell?",
            "type": "short-answer",
            "answer": "Thompson shell"
        }]
    }]
}
